DAVID **NGUYEN**

Unit 4 – 45 Salisbury Street, Canley Heights, 2166 · 0412 855 546 davidnguyen4898@gmail.com

I am a 4th year and studying a software engineering related degree, Bioinformatics Engineering. My goal is to be employed in a company with needs for software development to gain valuable work experience, refine my work ethic and further develop my software related skills. I am adaptable and quick learning and believe these qualities to be essential to a software engineering related role. I can assure that my abilities and adaptive skills can be effectively utilized for the role as a software engineer intern.

EXPERIENCE

21/1/2019 - 18/1/2020

DELIVERY DRIVER, PIZZA HUT

- Execution of POS systems for business transactions
- Ensure customer satisfaction and develop good customer relations
- Promoting goods and pitching sales to customers

27/6/2017 - CURRENTLY

RETAIL BAR AND FOOD ATENDANT, VENUESLIVE

- Execution of POS systems for business transactions
- Stock count/management
- Ensure customer satisfaction
- Maintaining a neat and tidy work environment

EDUCATION

JANUARY 2011 – DECEMBER 2016
YEAR 12 HSC, FAIRVALE HIGH SCHOOL

Awards:

- Caltex All-Rounder Award 2016

Achievement:

- 84.90 ATAR

FEBRUARY 2017 – CURRENTLY

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING – BIOINFORMATICS ENGINEERING, UNSW

Focus: Computer science and biology.

Achievement:

- COMP1511 (Introduction to Programming)
- COMP1531 (Software Engineering Fundamentals)
- COMP2041 (Software Construction)
- COMP2521 (Data Structure and Algorithms)

SKILLS

Area of Computing	Skills and Length of Experience	Level Skill
Languages	C++ Python JavaScript HTML and CSS SQL	Intermediate Intermediate Basic Basic Intermediate
Scripting	Shell Perl Python	Intermediate
Operating Systems	Unix/Linux	Intermediate

Teamwork

Able to effectively work together with a range of co-workers from diverse backgrounds in order to ensure gross satisfactory work performance. This is demonstrated through my extracurriculars and work experience.

Problem Solving

Able to analyses and swiftly diffuse situations conveyed through my experience in the workforce and extracurriculars. In relation to the position, I am also able to analyze computer exercises and solve them adequately demonstrated through my Distinction in COMP1511.

Languages

• Vietnamese: Fluent Oral

• English: Fluent oral and written

ACTIVITIES

Cabramatta Moon Festival

2016 - 2019

- Maintenance of event equipment and facilities
- Assisted management of volunteers
- Coordinated and assisted sales

Bring it on! Youth Festival

2016 - 2019

- Logistic support to ensure smooth running of the event
- Provided positive customer service
- Assisted in setting up the event equipment and facilities

REFEREES

Professional and academic referees available on request.